scripturetyper.com 2011-05-26

# Scripture Typer - Privacy Policy

## 1\. Information we collect

Members of the Scripture Typer website have the option of creating an account, in order to store memory verses and track their progress.  We store basic personal information which is voluntarily given by the user, such as a username, email address, and password.  We also allow members to store the following information which helps us provide a positive user experience while memorizing scripture.

1\. User preferences for interacting with the website  
2\. Statistics on verses memorized  
3\. Verses entered or selected by the user 

## 2\. Maintaining your information

All of your account information can be accessed from your User Profile page.  You will be taken to this page immediately after creating a new account.  To return to the user profile page later, hover your mouse over your name at the top right, and click 'My Profile'. 

## 3\. Email Communications

Scripture Typer makes use of email to contact members in certain situations.  Members may opt out of any or all forms of email communication from the User Profile page. 

1\. Weekly or Daily Review  
2\. Important Account or Web Site Updates  

Review is essential for successful scripture memorization, and all members will by default receive a weekly email detailing their memorization progress.  The frequency of this review can be changed or turned off from the User Profile page.  The options are Weekly Review, Daily Review and Do Not Review.  Select 'Do Not Review' to stop receiving all review reminders. 

Bugs do arise from time to time, and we may need to contact you if your account is effected in some way.  If you prefer not to be contacted, just deselect the option to be notified of important account updates on your user profile page. 

## 4\. Securing your information

All personal information collected by our website is stored on our secure server.  **Your information will never be shared or sold to any third party.**   Passwords are strongly encrypted, and are not retrievable.  In the event that you forget your password, please use our password recovery feature which will generate a new password and email it to you. 

## 5\. Our Privacy Policy

Our privacy policy may change from time to time, but rest assured that your personal information will always be kept secure and private.  New versions will be posted on this web site, so please check back periodically for updates.

If you have questions or feedback about this policy, please Contact Us.  
We love to hear from our members!
